mporn.com 2007-08-31

# M Porn

**Mobile Fusion Ltd. Privacy Policy.**

Mobile Fusion knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting mporn.com you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. What this privacy policy covers· This Privacy Policy covers treatment of personally identifiable information that collects when you are on the web site or mobile portal, and when you use services. This policy also covers treatment of any personally identifiable information that business partners share with or that may collect on a partner's site. · This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Mobile Fusion does not own or control, or to people that Mobile Fusion does not employ or manage. If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact the Privacy Manager by email at support@mporn.   
  
**Information Collection and Use:**

Mobile Fusion is the sole owner of the information collected on www.mporn.com and wap.mporn.com. Mobile Fusion collects information from our users only with their permission on our Web site and Mobile Portal.  

**Communications from the Site:**

Special Offers and Updates: Only when the user has specifically requested this type of information, will they receive information on products, services, special deals, and/or a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications.  
  
**Service Announcements:**

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. Users may opt-out of these communications.  
  
**Customer Service:**

We communicate with users to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.  
  
**Sharing:**

Legal Disclaimer: Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)We do share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.These are the instances in which we will share users' personal information:We DO NOT Share Personal Information with Third Parties.  
  
**Service Providers:**

We partner with other third parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these particular services, we share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.  
  
**Notification of Changes:**

This privacy policy covers the following Mobile Fusion sites:

http://www.mporn.com  
http://wap.mporn.com  
  
**Choice/Opt-out:**

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our sites at the point where we ask for information. Users who no longer wish to receive information and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the communication of by contacting us at email at support@mporn.com to opt-out.Users of our sites are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party.  
  
**Links:**

This Web sites may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Mobile Fusion, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.  
  
**Surveys & Contests:**

From time-to-time our sites may request information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as postal code). Contact information will be to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of our sites. Users' personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, they may not use users' personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.  
  
**Chat Rooms:**

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example, through e-mail, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.  
  
**Security:**

Mobile Fusion sites takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site or Mobile Portal, their information is protected both online and off-line.  
  
**Correcting, Updating, Deleting, and Deactivating Personal Information:** If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can be done by emailing our Customer Support at [support@mporn.com](mailto:support@mporn.com)  
  
**Contact Informantion:**

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us by email: [support@mporn.com](mailto:support@mporn.com)
